<journey name="Import accumulator from clipboard">
    <description>
        Exercises the clipboard-aware Utreexo accumulator import (issue #67): the on-open
        "Accumulator found on clipboard" snackbar and the "Paste from clipboard" button in
        the paste sheet.

        PRECONDITION: a valid Utreexo accumulator payload (JSON or "utreexo1…" compact form)
        FOR THE CURRENT NETWORK must be on the device clipboard, and the node must still be
        in initial block download (IBD) so the import card/sheet are available.

        There is no stable cross-version `adb` command to set the system clipboard. If the
        agent cannot place the payload on the clipboard (and cannot copy one from within the
        app), mark every clipboard-dependent action SKIPPED rather than FAILED.
    </description>
    <actions>
        <action>Launch the Mandacaru app and wait for the splash screen to dismiss (poll until nav_node is present)</action>
        <action>Verify the Node navigation item (nav_node) is selected and the node is in IBD (a sync progress percentage node_sync_percentage below 100% is shown)</action>
        <action>Best-effort: place a valid accumulator payload for the current network on the device clipboard (try `adb shell` clipboard helpers; if none work, SKIP the remaining clipboard steps)</action>
        <action>Relaunch the app (cold start) and wait until nav_node is present</action>
        <action>Verify an "Accumulator found on clipboard" snackbar with an "Import" action is shown (target by text); if no payload could be set, SKIP this step</action>
        <action>Tap the "Import" action on the snackbar (by text)</action>
        <action>Verify the paste sheet opens with its payload field pre-filled (the snapshot text is visible in the sheet)</action>
        <action>Dismiss the sheet by tapping "Cancel" (by text)</action>
        <action>Open the import card on the Node screen and tap its "Paste" entry to reopen the paste sheet</action>
        <action>Tap the "Paste from clipboard" button inside the sheet (by text)</action>
        <action>Verify the payload field becomes populated (valid clipboard) or an inline error "Clipboard does not contain a valid accumulator" is shown (empty/invalid clipboard), and the app has not crashed</action>
        <action>Tap the "Import" button (by text) and verify the import confirmation dialog appears showing the snapshot network and height</action>
    </actions>
</journey>
